Sky of golden sun,
Steppe of golden seed,
Legend of courage –
Take a look at my country!
From antiquity
Our heroic glory emerged,
They did not give up their pride
My Kazakh people are strong!
My country, my country,
As your flower I will be planted,
As your song I will stream, my country!
My native land – My Kazakhstan!
The way was opened to posterity
I have a vast land.
Its unity is proper,
I have an independent country.
It welcomed the time
Like an eternal friend,
Our country is happy,
Such is our country.
My country, my country,
As your flower I will be planted,
As your song I will stream, my country!
My native land – My Kazakhstan!
My country, my country,
As your flower I will be planted,
As your song I will stream, my country!
My native land – My Kazakhstan!